[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle：有一堆使用回调尝试过的非修复。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: There's a bunch of Non Fixes that have been attempted with callbacks.
我称它们为非修复，因为它们试图修复，实际上什么也做不了，只是
I call them Non Fixes cuz they're attempts at fixing which actually did nothing but
让事情变得更糟。
make it worse.
例如，在回调世界中，我们发明了这种拆分回调的模式。
So for example, in the callback world we invented this pattern of split callbacks.
如果我们试图解决的问题是我们有一个错误，而我们没有
If our problem that we're trying to solve is that we've got an error that we don't
如果主功能有问题，我想被吞噬，
wanna get swallowed in case there's some problem with the main function,
我们就像我知道我会为我的错误传递一个单独的回调。
we're like I know I'll just pass a separate callback for my errors.
那样的话，如果有一些错误，至少我
And that way if there is some error at least I
我知道公用事业公司会以某种方式通知我出现了问题，
know that utility will have some way of notifying me that there was a problem,
好吧，表面上听起来不错。
all right, sounds good on the surface.
直到你意识到这实际上使信任问题变得更糟。
Until you realize this actually makes the trust issue a lot worse.
因为现在你必须扪心自问，如果他们两个都不叫的话会发生什么
Because now you have to ask yourself what happens if they call neither of
这些功能？
these functions?
如果他们同时调用这两个函数会发生什么？
What happens if they call both of these functions?
也许他们先叫错误，然后叫成功。
Maybe they call the error first and then the success.
或者，也许他们先称成功，然后称错误。
Or maybe they call the success first and then the error.
你的程序将如何处理这个问题？
How is your program gonna handle that?
我打赌你们中的一些人有这样的代码，而你们还没有任何解决方案。
I bet some of you have code like this and you don't have any solution for that yet.
它实际上使问题变得更糟。
It actually made the problem worse.
还有更多的信任问题。
There's more trust issues.
因此，虽然在服务器上听起来不错，但拆分回调实际上是一种回归。
So split callbacks while it sounded good on the servers actually was a regression.
它把我们带离了一个好的解决方案。
It took us away from a good solution.
在节点世界中，我们发明了经常被称为节点样式的东西，
In the node world, we invented what often times referred to as node style,
我喜欢调用错误优先回调。
I like to call error first callbacks.
好吧，让我们回到一个回调，两个回调是疯狂的。
Well let's go back to one callback, two callbacks is crazy.
让我们回到一个回调。
Let's go back to one callback.
但我们将为错误信号保留该回调的第一个参数。
But we'll reserve the first parameter of that callback for the error signal.
所以如果我们在发信号通知它是一个错误，我们总是设置那个
So if it's an error that we're signaling, we'll always set that one and
没有其他的，如果它不是一个错误，那么我们将留下那个。
nothing else and if it's not an error then we'll leave that.
所以你写的每一个节点回调都有这个if else
And so every single node callback that you've ever written has this if else
爵士乐在里面进行着，你在那里检查是不是或者
jazz going on in it, where you're checking to see whether or
不是，这是不是一个错误条件。
not it's an error condition or not.
所以它似乎解决了拆分回调的问题，直到
So it seems like it solved the problem about the split callbacks thing until
你意识到实际上同样的问题也发生在这里。
you realize actually the same questions occur here.
如果所讨论的实用程序的行为与您预期的不同，会发生什么情况，
What happens if the utility in question does not behave the way you expect,
如果它两次回拨你的电话，一次是空中的，会发生什么？
what happens if it calls your call back twice, once with the air and
一次没有错误。
once with not the error.
或者如果它同时使用错误和成功参数调用会发生什么，
Or what happens if it calls with both the error and the success parameters,
你如何解释这种情况？
how do you interpret Interpret that situation?
所有同样的信任问题都在起作用。
All the same trust issues are at play.
我们没有从根本上控制回调，这意味着我们有
We are not fundamentally in control of the callback which means we have
把所有的控制权都颠倒了，然后把它交给了其他人。
inverted all that control and given it away to somebody else.
所以这些实际上是不能修复的。
So these are really non fixes.
现在我有一个愚蠢的运行示例，
Now I've got a silly running example,
你们中有多少人认识到生命的意义？
how many of you recognize the reference to the meaning of life?
希望我还没有老到只有我一个人知道“搭便车指南”(Hitchhiker‘s Guide)。
Hopefully I'm not so old that I'm the only one that knows about Hitchhiker's Guide.
如果你不知道，去读维基百科什么的，
If you don't know about that, go read Wikipedia, something,
加快速度。
get up to speed on it.
愚蠢的例子使用嵌套回调计算生活的意义。
Silly example calculating the meaning of life using nested callbacks.
这是我的Think Ajax调用，我的getData函数。
Here's my think Ajax call, my getData function.
因为它接受了一段数据，比如一个数字，并且
As it takes in a piece of data, like a number, and
然后在1000毫秒后，它调用我提供的任何回调
then after a 1000 milliseconds, it calls whatever callback I provided and
直接把数据发回去。
just sends the data right back.
所以我假装要问答案，值10的计算。
So I pretend to ask for the answer, the calculation of value 10.
1000毫秒后，调用该函数，并且num1是值10。
1000 milliseconds later, the function is called and num1 is the value 10.
现在x=1+10。
Now x = 1 + 10.
所以x是11。
So x is 11.
然后我打到30
And then I make the call to 30.
您注意到这是连续调用。
You notice that this is sequential calling.
我将这些调用嵌套在一起，因为它们具有时间依赖性，
I've nested these calls together because they have a temporal dependency,
直到我算完11，我才能算出31。
I can't calculate 31 until after I've calculated 11.
然后在计算完这两个之后，我把这两个放在一起，
And then after both of those have been calculated, then I put the two together,
生命的意义42。
meaning of life 42.
我要求在1000毫秒内计算，我得到了我的答案。
I ask for that from to be computed in 1000 milliseconds later I get my answer back.
生命的意义42。
Meaning of life 42.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[听不到]&gt；&gt；Kyle：是的，对不起，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [INAUDIBLE] &gt;&gt; Kyle: Yep sorry,
我们讨论的是getData调用的第5行和第7行。
we're talking about lines 5 and lines 7 for the getData calls.
生命意义的getData调用的第9行。
Line 9 for the getData call of meaning of life.
最后，答案回到第11行。
And then finally the answer is coming back on line 11.
谢天谢地，我的只花了1000毫秒
Thankfully mine only took 1000 milliseconds or
3，而不是数万亿年或其他什么。
3 instead of trillions of years or whatever.
对于setTimeout来说，这将是一个相当大的数字。
That would be a pretty big number for the setTimeout.
但您可以看到这里我有嵌套的回调。
But you see here I have the nested callbacks.
我有所有的问题，这甚至是非局部的非顺序推理。
And I have all the problems of, this is non-local non-sequential reasoning even.
是的，垂直方向，我可以穿过金字塔。
Yes, vertically, I can move through the pyramid.
但是当我将其中一个回调移动到另一个模块时会发生什么
But what happens when I move one of those callbacks into another module
我的效用？
of my utility?
现在我把这个非本地的跳转到其他地方来理解
Now I've got this non-local jump over to some other location to understand
发生了什么。
what's happening.
[咳嗽]在控制反转中我有所有的信任问题。
[COUGH] And I have all the trust issues in inversion of control.